https://www.columbiabc.edu/system-admin/privacy-policy

Future StudentsParentsAlumniCOVID-19
ApplyRequest InfoGive
Search:
Search
Quick Links
ProgramsApplyRequest InfoLibraryAcademic CalendarStudent Events CalendarBearcat AthleticsTranscript RequestsCBC BlogConferences & CateringOrientation Week
My CBC
Search:
Search
Admissions & AidWhy Columbia?Explore Your CallingGrad CareersLocation MattersVirtual View Days & Program Info SessionsInfo for US StudentsApplyHow to ApplyEntrance RequirementsAdmissions TeamFAQThe Refer-A-Student BonusProgramsCertificatesDiplomas & DegreesOnline & Casual StudiesNorth Shore School of MissionCostsTuition & FeesCost CalculatorFinancial AidStudent Loans & Payment PlansRequest InfoApply NowStudent LifeThe CampusRes LifeCommuter LifeDining ServicesCampus MapVirtual TourLife TogetherOur CommunityGet InvolvedWorshipStudent LeadershipExpectationsStudent ServicesBookstoreParking & SecurityStudent Job BoardHousing BoardStudent DiscountsResourcesAcademic SupportCounselling ServicesLibrary HomepageSafe CommunityOrientation Week ScheduleStudent EventsOrientation Week ScheduleAcademicsProgramsCertificatesDiplomas & DegreesWhy Practical Theology?Online & Casual StudiesCredit TransfersRegistrationCourse RegistrationCourse DescriptionsAcademic CalendarTimetablesIntegrated LearningService PracticumInternshipsUrban Mission DynamicsAcademic PoliciesTranscripts & SyllabiTransfer GuidesAcademic ManualParchment ReplacementAcademic CalendarAthleticsVarsityBasketball RostersBB Schedule & ResultsVolleyball RostersVB Schedule & ResultsNews & HighlightsWatch OnlineInside BearcatsBearcat CultureRecruitmentCoaches & StaffCampus RecFacilities & EquipmentGet InvolvedCheer Us OnCorporate SponsorshipsAdopt-a-BearcatInvest Your TimeCommunityAlumniColumbia AlumniA-CardAlumni DiscountsAlumni Update FormStay ConnectedSupport ColumbiaThe Coffee InitiativePrayFund a ScholarshipGive OnlineColumbia Open GolfColumbia Annual Fundraising Dinner - Oct 26Churches & CommunityEducators SeminarChurch ResourcesChurch Match BursaryCamp Match BursaryMetzger CollectionContinuing EducationConferences & CateringRental SpacesAccommodationsCommunity EventsAboutColumbiaMission StatementConfession of FaithOur StoryAccredidationAffiliationsLeadershipPresident's MessageLEAD TeamBoard of DirectorsPublicationsColumbia Contact MagazineReportsColumbia BlogContact UsLocationStaff & Faculty DirectoryEmploymentStudent Events Calendar
APPLY
Privacy Policy
Introduction
We have created this statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. We do not collect personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. This policy is your guide to how we will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our Web site.
(Columbia's overall Privacy Policy is also available.)
Use of Links
Throughout our Web pages, we provide links to other servers which may contain information of interest to our readers. We take no responsibility for, and exercise no control over, the organizations, views, or accuracy of the information contained on other servers. Creating a text link from your Web site to our site does not require permission. If you have a link you'd like us to consider adding to our Web site, please send an email to webmaster@columbiabc.edu with the subject "Link request."
Use of Text and Images
If you would like to publish information that you find on our Web site, please send your request to webmaster@columbiabc.edu. Where text or images are posted on our site with the permission of the original copyright holder, a copyright statement appears at the bottom of the page. Information about using our logo and images is available in Media Resources.
Accessibility
This Web site is designed to be accessible to visitors with disabilities, and to comply with federal guidelines concerning accessibility. We welcome your comments. If you have suggestions on how to make the site more accessible, please contact us at webmaster@columbiabc.edu.
Reading or Downloading
We collect and store only the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account, or princeton.edu if you are connecting from Princeton University's domain), the date and time you access our site, and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked to our site.
We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors.
Online Profile Updates and Donations
If you complete the Profile update form and share your personally identifying information, this information will be used only to provide you with more targeted content. We may use your contact information to send further information about our organization or to contact you when necessary. You may always opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the "Opt Out" section below.
Sending us an Email
You also may decide to send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message containing a question or comment, or by filling out a Web form that provides us this information. We use personally identifying information from email primarily to respond to your requests. We may forward your email to other employees who are better able to answer you questions. We may also use your email to contact you in the future about our programs that may be of interest.
We want to be very clear: We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. Except as might be required by law, we do not share any information we receive with any outside parties.
If you sign up for one of our email lists, we will only send you the kinds of information you have requested. We won't share your name or email address with any outside parties.
Kids and Privacy
For children who visit our site, special rules apply. We do not request personal information about children, such as first and last name or street address and city. When kids send email to us, their online contact information (email address) is not used to re-contact them and is not maintained in retrievable form.
Opt-Out or Change Your Contact Information
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us through a special online form. You may choose to receive only specific communications or none at all. You may also update your contact information previously provided to us through another online form. You can not remove yourself from our database, but you can prevent unwanted communication.
Cookies
Columbiabc.edu uses third-party advertising (including Facebook Adverts and Google Adwords) to show you targeted advertisements about our college as you move around the web. This targeting is achieved through cookies (small pieces of data) and conversion pixels that send information from our website to Google, Facebook and other online advertising networks. Any information collected is anonymous and does not contain visitor name or contact information. For more information about third-party advertising, your privacy and your opt-out options, please visit:
Google's Ads Settings page.
Facebook’s ‘About Advertising Page.’
The Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
Questions about our Policies
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at webmaster@columbiabc.edu.
